{"data":[{"question":"The fortune teller sounds ___.","a":"pleasantly","b":"nicely","c":"wonderfully","d":"friendly","answer":"4","explain":"- An adjective always follows a sense verb or a verb of appearance\u00a0- feel, taste, smell, sound, look, appear, and seem - when it modifies the noun before the verb.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"They'll get _________ by taxi if they ser off right now.","a":"there enough fast","b":"fast enough there","c":"there fast enough","d":"enough fast there","answer":"3","explain":"- Adverb\/adj + enough","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"A teacher at a big cram school says this is ___ for the beginners.","a":"the too difficult content","b":"too difficult the content","c":"difficult too the content","d":"too difficult content","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Too adjective\u00a0for somebody to do do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Dr. Jackson returned from China yesterday. He brought back ___ bowl.","a":"an old Chinese delicate earthenware","b":"a Chinese old delicate earthenware","c":"a delicate old Chinese earthenware","d":"an earthenware old delicate Chinese","answer":"3","explain":"- Adjective order: Opinion- size- age- shape-color- origin-material- purpose\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Would you like to join our team? \"Sorry, I am not ___ as any of you.\"","a":"so good a player","b":"as a good player","c":"a so good player","d":"a player so good","answer":"1","explain":"- Adjective + Noun\u00a0\n- Not so ... as ... : used in comparisons to say that something or someone has less of a particular quality than another person or thing","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Do you like the Chinese food served in McDonalds? \"It's not bad but I prefer ___\"","a":"Chinese food authentic","b":"Chinese food authentically","c":"authentic Chinese food","d":"Chinese authentic","answer":"3","explain":"- Adjective order: Opinion- size- age- shape-color- origin-material- purpose\u00a0","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"We found ___.","a":"hard to do the work","b":"the work hard for doing","c":"the work was hard to do","d":"it hard for doing the work","answer":"3","explain":"- Find something + adjective\u00a0\n- Be adjective to do sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"You'd better be sure to wash your face ___.","a":"cleaning","b":"cleaned","c":"clean","d":"to be clean","answer":"3","explain":"- Wash sth+ adjective","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"The examination was ___ easier than we had expected.","a":"much","b":"more","c":"more much","d":"much more","answer":"1","explain":"-Much \/ More + Adj\u00a0\n+Use much (adv.) to emphasize a comparative adjective, -er.","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"},{"question":"Daniel's co-workers were not ___ at his being dismissed.","a":"the least surprising","b":"less surprised","c":"the least surprised","d":"the lesser surprised","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the superlatives of long adjective (surprised)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"7","subcategorylv2":"6","type":"1"}]}